As cities balloon with growth, access to nature for people living in urban areas is becoming harder to find.
随着城市迅速扩张，生活在城市地区的人们正越来越难以接触到自然。
If you’re lucky, there might be a pocket park near where you live, but it’s unusual to find places in a city that are relatively wild.
运气好的话，你住的地方附近可能会有一个口袋公园，但在城市里很少能找到相对原生态的地方。
Past research has found health and wellness benefits of nature for humans, but a new study shows that wildness in urban areas is extremely important for human well-being.
过去的研究已经发现自然对人类健康和身心安康有益，但一项新研究表明，城市地区的野性自然对人类福祉极其重要。
The research team focused on a large urban park.
研究团队以一座大型城市公园为研究对象。
They surveyed several hundred park-goers, asking them to submit a written summary online of a meaningful interaction they had with nature in the park.
他们调查了几百名公园游客，请他们在网上提交一份书面总结，讲述自己在公园里与自然的一次有意义的互动。
The researchers then examined these submissions, coding experiences into different categories.
研究人员随后仔细查看了这些提交的内容，把各种体验编码，归入不同的类别。
For example, one participant’s experience of “We sat and listened to the waves at the beach for a while” was assigned the categories “sitting at beach” and “listening to waves.”
例如，一位参与者的体验“我们坐在海滩上听了一会儿海浪声”，被归入“坐在海滩上”和“倾听海浪”这两个类别。
Across the 320 submissions, a pattern of categories the researchers call a “nature language” began to emerge.
在全部320份提交内容中，一种类别模式开始显现，研究人员称之为“自然语言”。
After the coding of all submissions, half a dozen categories were noted most often as important to visitors.
在对所有提交内容完成编码后，有六个类别最常被记录为对游客很重要。
These include encountering wildlife, walking along the edge of water, and following an established trail.
其中包括邂逅野生动物、沿水边散步和沿着既有的步道行走。
Naming each nature experience creates a usable language, which helps people recognize and take part in the activities that are most satisfying and meaningful to them.
为每一种自然体验命名，就形成了一种可用的语言，它能帮助人们识别并参与那些最让自己满足、对自己最有意义的活动。
For example, the experience of walking along the edge of water might be satisfying for a young professional on a weekend hike in the park.
例如，对一个周末在公园徒步的年轻上班族来说，沿水边散步的体验可能会令人满足。
Back downtown during a workday, they can enjoy a more domestic form of this interaction by walking along a fountain on their lunch break.
等到工作日回到市中心，这位上班族可以在午休时沿着喷泉散步，以一种更人工化、不那么野性的形式享受这种互动。
“We’re trying to generate a language that helps bring the human-nature interactions back into our daily lives.
“我们正努力创造一种语言，帮助把人与自然的互动带回我们的日常生活。
And for that to happen, we also need to protect nature so that we can interact with it,” said Peter Kahn, a senior author of the study.
而要实现这一点，我们还需要保护自然，这样我们才能与之互动。”该研究的资深作者之一彼得·卡恩说。